RESUME

PERSONAL PARTICULARS

	Name	David Yan Dawei
	Date of Birth	28 April 1992
	Contact (HP)	(65) 91160105
	Email	davidyan.sxc@gmail.com
	Linkedin	https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-yan92/

PROFILE

A self-driven individual interested in using data to solve business problems and drive better client value. Knowledgeable in Object Oriented Programming, Python, Machine Learning techniques, Git, and Amazon Web Services. Experienced in agile software development methodology.

EXPERIENCE

STUDENT, GENERAL ASSEMBLY

NOV 2017-FEB 2018

* Used supervised machine learning techniques to rank and identify factors that affect romantic relationships to minimise risk of failure for couples.

BUSINESS ANALYST, OPPOIN PTE LTD

AUG 2016-AUG 2017

* Built quotation processing system to streamline client quotation process by integrating payment pipeline, enabling faster disbursement and increasing customer satisfaction

INDEPENDENT CONTRACTOR, AON HEWITT PTE LTD

MAR 2015-JUL 2016

* Cooperated with Aon consultants to build HR tools which helps improve business workflow, prevent resource overload and increase employee engagement

RISK ANALYST (INTERN), STANDARD CHARTERED PLC

JUL 2012-OCT 2012

* Reported and highlighted project schedule, risks and issues to project lead to ensure successful project delivery

EDUCATION

General Assembly, Singapore - Data Science Immersive November 2017 - February 2018

Nanyang Technological University, Singapore – Degree in philosophy October 2015 - June 2016, left in July 2016 Institute of Banking & Finance, Singapore – IBF Qualified for Technology & Operations (operations), attained in February 2015

IBF Singapore, Financial Industry Competency Standards - Acquire & Apply Financial Markets Industry & Product Knowledge (Degree 4), attained in March 2013

Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore – Diploma in Financial Business Informatics March 2010 to April 2013

Chartered Institute for Securities & Investment - CISI Level 3 Certificate in Wealth Management, attained in November 2012

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES:

- PHP
- Python
- Javascript
- * SQL

SOFTWARE:

- Laravel
- ♦ Git
- * Amazon Web Service, EC2, S3
- Linux, Ubuntu
- * Confluence